gptoday.com 2019-02-07

# F1, Formula 1: GPToday.com- Privacy Policy

GP Today and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

During the process of delivering our content to you, GP Today does not collect any personally identifiable information about you - such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address without your knowledge and unless you provide it.

Information such as a User Name and your email address is required to join GP Today's mailing list, 'PPP Competition', the Forums and the News Grab Service or when using the Contact/Feedback form, but this information is not shared or sold to any other party. We will also store any preferences you set while you are logged in, such as News Sources and your default view.

Through third party web site analytics tools (Such As Google Analytics and Clicky) and the Contact/Feedback Form, some types of non-personally identifiable information about its visitors is collected - such as time of visit, browser type, which page(s) were viewed, the type of operating system, screen resolution and screen colours which may be linked to individual visitors. This information is used to assist GP Today in producing web pages more suited to its average visitor. Your IP address will also be collected. The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better.

Some 3rd parties like Facebook and Twitter may know you visited this website, if you use their services. We can’t control them but we don’t believe this knowledge poses any threat to you.

To allow visitors to discuss our articles and some web pages we use a discussion system called Disqus. Disqus anonymously tracks visitors to pages like we do. They also remember who you are if you login to any Disqus service, so you can comment on any website using their tool.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.

We use Cookies on this Site. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's web browser while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience. Persistent Cookies can be removed or blocked by following the help file directions in your Internet browser. If you elect to block Cookies, you may not be able to access certain personalised sections of our website.
